Welcome back to the Athleadership Arena.
In our first lesson, you suited up to commit to your championship season.
Today, we begin what every elite athlete undergoes before they ever step onto the field.
Pre-season conditioning.
This isn't about running laps.
This is about deep inner work.
Think of it as your rear-view mirror, a moment, a chance to look back, take the lessons from
your life's journey, and make meaning from them.
Before you begin to build a game plan for your future, you need a clear and honest scatter
report of yourself.
We call this your inner blueprint.
It's the unique combination of your values, your strengths, your life experiences, and
your energy patterns.
The primary A.R.A.W. muscles we are conditioning in this lesson are your wellbeing through
deep self-awareness and your resilience by learning from your past.
In a world where change is constant, this is your inner and anchor core.
The stronger your inner blueprint, the more agile you can become in uncertainty.
This lesson is about giving yourself the room to gather the essential raw materials.
This is what you'll need to architect your M.V.P. blueprint in our next lesson.